Guide to the Columbia Unoversity Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Columbia University Press Records,
1893-[ca. 1960],
1923-[1960] (bulk)
Columbia University. Press.
117 linear ft (ca. 140,000 items in 270 boxes).
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
4078645
History
The Columbia University Press, one of the oldest and largest of American university presses, was founded in 1893. The Press has published dissertations and other works by academic authors from Columbia University and elsewhere, series of books and other publications for departments of the University, periodicals, and other works.
Scope and Content
Editorial files dating primarily from the reorganization of the Press in 1923 by Frederick Coykendall.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 4 series:
Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
Series II: Arranged Files
Series III: Office Files
Series IV: Columbia University Press - Printed Materials
Subjects
Coykendall, Frederick, 1872-1954.; University presses--New York (State)--New York.; Publishers and publishing--New York (State)--New York.; Account books.; Announcements.; Annual reports.; Budgets.; Catalogs.; Financial reccords.; Minutes.; Personnel records.
Access Restrictions
This collection is licated off-site. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
This collection has no restrictions.
Acquisition
1919 M-19 Columbia University Press Gift
Alternate Formats
Pearl S. Buck letter is on microfilm.
Royal Cortissoz lettrers are on microfilm.
Gift of the Press, 1919 & 1978.
- Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
  - Abbe, Catherine Amory Palmer (Mrs Robert)
  - Adler, Elmer
  - Adler, Mortimer
  - Anderson, Margaret
  - Angell, James Rowland
  - Ansen, Alan J.
  - Aptheker, Herbert
  - Armour, Richard
  - Arms, John Taylor
  - Armstrong, Edwin Howard
  - Arnold, Thurman Wesley
  - Atkinson, Brooks
  - Aydelotte, Frank
  - Baker, Carlos Heard
  - Baker, Ray Stannard
  - Bakhmeteff, Boris Alexander
  - Barnes, Harry Elmer
  - Bartók, Bélla Letters & manuscripts
  - Barzun, Henri Martin
  - Beard, Charles Austin
  - Belmont, Perry
  - Benedict, Ruth Fulton
  - Benét, William Rose
  - Benjamin, Park, II
  - Bennet, William Stiles
  - Bentley, Eric Russell
  - Berle, Adolf Augustus, Jr.
  - Bernays, Edward L
  - Bingham, Millicent Todd
  - Bird, Elisha Brown
  - Blumenthal, Joseph
  - Boas, Franz
  - Bowman, Isaiah
  - Browder, Earl Russel
  - Buck, Pearl Sydenstricker
    [Available on microfilm]
  - Burgess, Gelett
  - Burgess, John William
  - Burgess, Ruth Payne Jewett (Mrs John William)
  - Burns, Arthur Francis
  - Burton, Harold Hitz
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray
  - Canby, Henry Seidel
  - Cane, Melville Henry
  - Capps, Edward
  - Cardozo, Benjamin Nathan
  - Carmer, Carl Lamson
  - Cary, Melbert Brinckerhoff, Jr.
  - Cattell, James McKeen
  - Catton, Bruce
  - Cazamian, Louis
  - Chase, Lewis Nathaniel
  - Chase, Mary Ellen
  - Clemens, Cyril
  - Cohn, Adolphe Contracts
  - Colby, Elbridge
  - Cole, Frank Nelson
  - Colum, Mary Gunning Maguire (Mrs Padraic)
  - Colum, Padraic
  - Commager, Henry Steele Includes manuscripts
  - Conant, James Bryant
  - Corey, Lewis
  - Cortissoz, Royal
  - Coudert, Frederic René
  - Cousins, Norman
  - Creekmore, Hubert
  - Darlington, James Henry
  - Darrow, Whitney
  - Davis, Elmer Holmes
  - De Lima, Agnes
  - Dewey, John
  - Donovan, William Joseph
  - Douglas, Lewis Williams
  - Douglas, Paul Howard
  - Drinkwater, John
  - Duggan, Stephen
  - Dulles, Foster Rhea
  - Edgett, Edwin Francis
  - Egbert, James Chidester
  - Einstein, Lewis David
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David
  - Erskine, John Includes manuscripts
  - Evans, Ernestine
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield
  - Fiske, Thomas Scott
  - Flexner, Abraham
  - Forbes, Edward Waldo
  - Ford, Charles Henri
  - Ford, Guy Stanton
  - Fosdick, Harry Emerson
  - Foster, William Z.
  - Fox, Dixon Ryan
  - Frankenberg, Lloyd
  - Freeman, Douglas Southall
  - Freeman, Joseph
  - Fremantle, Anne Jackson
  - Freuchen, Peter
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth
  - Gilder, Rodinan
  - Granniss, Ruth Shepard
  - Greenslet, Ferris
  - Grierson, Sir Herbert John Clifford
  - Griffith, William
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert Hovey
  - Gulick, Luther Halsey
  - Hagedorn, Hermann
  - Hand, Learned
  - Hare, Richard Gilbert
  - Hayakawa, Samuel Ichiye
  - Hazard, Caroline
  - Hazard, Paul
  - Hewitt, Erskine
  - Hiss, Alger
  - Hobhouse, Leonard Trelawney
  - Hogan, Frank Smithwick
  - Holmes, John Haynes
  - Hough, George Anthony, Jr.
  - Hu Shih
  - Hughes, Charles Evans
  - Huntington, Archer Milton
  - Huxley, Sir Julian Sorell
  - Ickes, Harold Le Clair
  - James, Henry, 1879-1947
  - Jázzi, Oscar
  - Jessup, Philip Caryl
  - Jones, Howard Mumford
  - Kallen, Horace Meyer
  - Kellogg, Paul Underwood
  - Kennan, George Frost
  - Kent, Henry Watson
  - Keppel, Frederick Paul
  - Klebs, Arnold Carl
  - Knickerbocker, William Skinkle
  - Korzybski, Alfred
  - Kredel, Fritz
  - Krock, Arthur
  - Lamont, Corliss
  - Lamprecht, Sterling Power
  - Lasker, Bruno
  - Lang, Paul Henry
  - Laski, Harold Joseph
  - Lawrence, David
  - Leach, Henry Goddard
  - Ley, Willy
  - Loveman, Amy
  - Low, Benjamin Robbins Curtis
  - Low, Seth
  - Löwenstein-Wertheim-Freudenberg, Hubertus, Prinz zu
  - McBride, Mary Margaret
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell
  - Macdonald, Dwight
  - Macgowan, Kenneth
  - McWilliams, Carey
  - Malone, Dumas
  - Maritain, Jacques
  - Markel, Lester
  - Matsudaira, Tsuneo
  - Matthews, Brander
  - May, Rollo
  - Mead, Margaret
  - Meloney, William Brown
  - Mencken, Henry Louis
  - Menninger, Karl August
  - Menuhin, Yehudi
  - Meyer, Annie Nathan
  - Miller, Alice Duer
  - Miller, Dickinson Sergeant
  - Mills, Frederick Cecil
  - Mills, Odgen Livingston
  - Moholy-Nagy, Sybil Dorothy Peech (Mrs Laszlo)
  - Moley, Raymond
  - Montagu, Ashley
  - Moore, Douglas Stuart
  - Morley, Christopher
  - Mumford, Lewis
  - Murray, Gilbert Includes receipts
  - Murray, Robert Henry
  - Nabokov, Vladimir
  - Nevins, Allan
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold
  - Odell, George Clinton Densmore
  - Opdycke, John Baker
  - Osborn, Henry Fairfield Contracts
  - Parsons, Elsie Worthington Clews (Mrs Herbert)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes
  - Pell, Herbert Claiborne
  - Penrose, Boies
  - Perkins, Dexter
  - Pitkin, Walter Boughton
  - Pollock, Channing
  - Pope, Arthur Upham
  - Porter, Katherine Anne Includes manuscripts
  - Pottle, Frederick Albert
  - Randolph, Asa Philip
  - Rankin, John Elliott
  - Read., Conyers
  - Reik, Theodor
  - Riddell, William Renwick
  - Robinson, Henry Morton
  - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich
  - Rodman, Selden
  - Rogers, Bruce
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor Roosevelt
  - Roth, Ernest David
  - Rukeyser, Muriel
  - Ruzicka, Rudolph Includes drawing
  - Sadleir, Michael
  - Saito, Hirosi
  - Salvemini, Gaetano
  - Sansom, Sir George Bailey
  - Sarton, George
  - Schapiro, Meyer
  - Scherman, Harry
  - Schieffelin, William Jay
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Meier
  - Schoenberg, Arnold
  - Schuster, Max Lincoln
  - Scott, Mary Augusta
  - Seligman, Edwin Robert Anderson
  - Sforza, Carlo, Count
  - Shaw, Albert
  - Shibusawa, Eiichi, Viscount
  - Shotwell, James Thomson
  - Smith, David Eugene
  - Smith, Munroe
  - Spingarn, Amy Einstein (Mrs Joel E.)
  - Spingarn, Joel Elias
  - Steegmuller, Francis Joseph
  - Stettinius, Edward R., Jr.
  - Stevens, Wallace
  - Stevenson, Burton Egbert
  - Stokes, Isaac Newton Phelps
  - Stone, Harlan Fiske
  - Sukhotina, (Countess) Tatiana Lvovna Tolstaia
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays
  - Swallow, Alan
  - Swing, Raymond Gram
  - Taft, Robert Alfonso
  - Tate, Allen
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon
  - Thomson, Virgil
  - Tindall, William York
  - Tinker, Edward Larocque
  - Toynbee, Arnold Joseph
  - Trent, William Peterfield Contracts only
  - Trilling, Lionel
  - Trollope, Muriel Rose
  - Tugwell, Rexford Guy
  - Valentine, Lewis Joseph
  - Vanderbilt, Amy
  - Van Doren, Irita Bradford
  - Van Doren, Mark
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison
  - Watson, Thomas John
  - Weeks, Raymond
  - Welles, Sumner
  - Whalen, Grover A.
  - Wheelock, John Hall
  - White, Horace
  - White, William Anthony Parker "Anthony Boucher"
  - Willey, Basil
  - Williams, Eric
  - Williams, John Sharp
  - Williams, Talcott
  - Wilson, Edmund Beecher
  - Wilson, Woodrow
  - Woodberry, George Edward
  - Woods, Katherine Irvin
  - Woodward, Benjamin Duryea
  - Wright, Quincy
  - Zukofsky, Celia Thaew (Mrs Louis)
- Series II: Arranged Files
  - Aa - Abn (Box 1)
  - Abel, Theodora Mead (Box 1)
  - Abel, Theodore (Box 1)
  - Abelarde, Pedro Emmanuel (Box 1)
  - Abr - Abs (Box 1)
  - Abrahamsen, David (Box 1)
  - Abruzzi, Adam (Box 1)
  - Ac (Box 2)
  - Ackerman, Carl W. (Box 2)
  - Ad - Add (Box 2)
  - Adams (Box 2)
  - Adams, Evelyn Crady (Box 2)
  - Adams, George Plimpton (Box 2)
  - Adams, Henry Hitch (Box 2)
  - Addison, James Thayer (Box 2)
  - Ade - Af (Box 2)
  - Adler, Felix (Box 2)
  - Ag - Ak (Box 2)
  - Aga-Oglu, Mehmet (Box 2)
  - Aguirre, Jose Antonio de (Box 2)
  - Ala-Aid (Box 3)
  - Alabama Act No.888 (Box 3)
  - Albrecht-Carrié, Rene (Box 3)
  - Ale - Alk (Box 3)
  - Alexander (Box 3)
  - Alexander, Edward Porter (Box 3)
  - Alexander, Robert Jackson (Box 3)
  - Alexinsky, Gregoire (Box 3)
  - Alien Property Custodian (Box 3)
  - Alihan, Milla Aïssa (Box 3)
  - Alla - Alib (Box 3)
  - Allen (Box 3)
  - Allen, Harry Kenneth (Box 3)
  - Allen, Warren Dwight (Box 3)
  - Alli-Alt (Box 3)
  - Alpert, Harry (Box 3)
  - Aly, Bower (Box 3)
  - Ama - Amb (Box 3)
  - Amadeo, Santos Primo (Box 3)
  - Ambrose, Sr. Mary (Box 3)
  - American (Box 4)
  - American Alpine Club (Box 4)
  - American Assembly (Box 4)
  - American Association of Social Workers (Box 4)
  - American Book Center (Box 4)
  - American Book Publishers Bureau - War Committee (Box 4)
  - American Book Publishers Council, Inc. (Box 4)
  - American Booksellers Associations, Inc (Box 4)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 4)
  - American Council on Education (Box 4)
  - American Group Therapy Association (Box 4)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts (Box 4)
  - American Jewish Committee (Box 4)
  - American Library Association (Box 4)
  - American Museum of Natural History (Box 4)
  - American Musicological Society (Box 4)
  - American Ophthalmological Society (Box 5)
  - American Press Institute (Box 6)
  - American Slavic & East European Review (Box 6)
  - American Speech (Box 6)
  - Ames (Box 7)
  - Amherst College (Box 7)
  - Amos, Flora Rose (Box 7)
  - Anchel, Robert (Box 7)
  - Anderson (Box 7)
  - Anderson, Charles Roberts (Box 7)
  - Andrade, Manuel José (Box 7)
  - Andrade, Margarette de (Box 7)
  - Andre - Andrz (Box 7)
  - Andrews (Box 7)
  - Andrews, Avery Delano (Box 7)
  - Ang - Ant (Box 7)
  - Anglo Saxon Poetic Records (Box 7)
  - Anspacher, Abraham Samuel (Box 7)
  - Anstensen, Ansten (Box 7)
  - Ap (Box 7)
  - Appleton, William Worthen (Box 7)
  - Aptheker, Herbert (Box 7)
  - Ara - Arl (Box 7)
  - Arciniegas, German (Box 7)
  - , Archives of Psychology (Box 7)
  - Arma - Army (Box 7)
  - Armstrong (Box 7)
  - Armstrong, Elizabeth Howard (Box 7)
  - Am - Arv (Box 8)
  - Arnold, Arthur Zapolsky (Box 8)
  - Aronovici, Carol (Box 8)
  - Arrington, Joseph Earl (Box 8)
  - As (Box 8)
  - Asheim, Lester (Box 8)
  - Association of American University Presses (1) (Box 8)
  - Association of American University Presses (2) (Box 9)
  - Association of the Bar of the City of New York (Box 9)
  - At (Box 9)
  - Athanas, Emanuel S. (Box 9)
  - Atiya, A.S. (Box 9)
  - Atkinson, Geoffroy (Box 9)
  - Atlases (Box 9)
  - Atwater, Elton (Box 9)
  - Au (Box 10)
  - Aufricht, Hans (Box 10)
  - Ausubel, Herman (Box 10)
  - Av - Az (Box 10)
  - Axt, Richard G. (Box 10)
  - Ayres & Garwick Records (Box 10)
  - Ayres, Harry Morgan (Box 10)
  - Babcock (Box 10)
  - Babcock, Emily Atwater & A.C. Krey (Box 10)
  - Babenroth, Adolph Charles (Box 10)
  - Babo - Bac (Box 10)
  - Bach, Matthew Gruenberg (Box 10)
  - Bad. - Bah (Box 10)
  - Baehne, George Walter (Box 10)
  - Bagster-Collins, Elijah William (Box 10)
  - Bagster-Collins, Jeremy Felix (Box 10)
  - Bai - Baj (Box 11)
  - Bailey (Box 11)
  - Bailey, Joseph Cannon (Box 11)
  - Bailey, Stephen Kemp (Box 11)
  - Bainton, Roland H. (Box 11)
  - Baird (Box 11)
  - Baker (Box 11)
  - Baker, Benjamin (Box 11)
  - Baker, Elizabeth Faulkner (Box 11)
  - Bakhmeteff, Boris A. (Box 11)
  - Bal - Bale (Box 11)
  - Balakian, Anna (Box 11)
  - Baldwin (Box 11)
  - Baldwin, Charles Sears (Box 11)
  - Ball (Box 11)
  - Balo - Bam (Box 11)
  - Balz, Albert George Adam (Box 11)
  - Ban (Box 12)
  - Bancroft (Box 12)
  - Bandholtz, Harry Hill (Box 12)
  - Banks Theodore. Howard (Box 12)
  - Bar (Box 12)
  - Bard, Samuel (Box 12)
  - Barker (Box 12)
  - Barker, Joseph Edmund. (Box 12)
  - Barker, Richard Hindry (Box 12)
  - Barlach, Ernst (Box 12)
  - Barlow (Box 12)
  - Barn.... (Box 12)
  - Barnard, Frederick Augustus Porter (Box 12)
  - Barnard College (Box 12)
  - Barnes (Box 12)
  - Barnes, Homer Francis (Box 12)
  - Barnouw, Adriaan Jacob (Box 12)
  - Barnouw, Erik (Box 12)
  - Baron, Salo Wittmayer (Box 13)
  - Barr, Jessica H. (Box 14)
  - Barr, Lockwood (Box 14)
  - Barrett (Box 14)
  - Barri - Bars (Box 14)
  - Barry, Frederick (Box 14)
  - Barry, Josephine (Box 14)
  - Bart... (Box 14)
  - Bartlett, Adeline Courtney (Box 14)
  - Bartók, Béla (Box 14)
  - Barton, Charles Randolph (Box 14)
  - Barzilai, Genuna (Box 14)
  - Barzun, Jacques (Box 14)
  - Bas - Bat (Box 14)
  - Basch, Anton (Box 14)
  - Bates, Ernest Sutherland (Box 14)
  - Bates, Lindell Theodore (Box 14)
  - Bau - Baz (Box 15)
  - Bauer (Box 15)
  - Bauer, Elizabeth Kelley (Box 15)
  - Baumgartner, Apollinaris William (Box 15)
  - Bayrn, Max Isaac (Box 15)
  - Be (Box 15)
  - Beard, William (Box 15)
  - Beardsley, Wilfred Attwood (Box 15)
  - Beatie, Arthur Y. (Box 15)
  - Beatty, Edward Corbyn Obert (Box 15)
  - Beatty, Frederika (Box 15)
  - Beaty, John Owen (Box 15)
  - Beaumont de la Bonni Gustave Auguste (Box 15)
  - Beaver, Joseph (Box 15)
  - Bec (Box 16)
  - Beck (Box 16)
  - Beck, Hubert Park (Box 16)
  - Becker, Joseph M. (Box 16)
  - Beckett, Grace Louise (Box 16)
  - Beckhart, Benjamin Haggott (Box 16)
  - Beckwith, Burnham P. (Box 16)
  - Bed. - Bee (Box 16)
  - Beder (Box 16)
  - Beer (Box 16)
  - Beer, George Louis (Box 16)
  - Beers, Clifford Whittingham (Box 16)
  - Beesley, Patricia (Mrs W.R. Irwin) (Box 16)
  - Beh - Bei (Box 16)
  - Bel - Bern (Box 17)
  - Beicher, Wyatt Winton (Box 17)
  - Bell (Box 17)
  - Bell, Clair Hayden (Box 17)
  - Belmont, I. J. (Box 17)
  - Belmont, Perry (Box 17)
  - Bena - Benj (Box 17)
  - Bender (Box 17)
  - Benedict, Ruth Fulton (Box 17)
  - Bengis, Jerome (Box 17)
  - Benne, Kenneth D. (Box 17)
  - Bennett (Box 17)
  - Bens - Benz (Box 17)
  - Benson, Adolph Burnett (Box 17)
  - Bentle (Box 17)
  - Bentley, Harold Woodmansee (Box 17)
  - Berelson, Bern (Box 17)
  - Berenda, Ruth W. (Box 17)
  - Berg (Box 17)
  - Berger (Box 17)
  - Berger, Morroe (Box 17)
  - (Henry) Bergh Foundation (Box 17)
  - Bergh and Winner, Inc. (Box 17)
  - Bergson, Abram (Box 17)
  - Bergson, Henri (Box 17)
  - Berk (Box 18)
  - Berkson, Isaac Baer (Box 18)
  - Berlau, Abraham Joseph (Box 18)
  - Ben - Berm (Box 18)
  - Berle, Jr., Adolf Augustus (Box 18)
  - Bern (Box 18)
  - Bernard (Box 18)
  - Bernard, Theos (Box 18)
  - Bernardin, Joseph Buchanan (Box 18)
  - Bernstein (Box 18)
  - Bernstein, Benjamin M. (Box 18)
  - Bernstein, Harry (Box 18)
  - Berr - Bert (Box 18)
  - Berry (Box 18)
  - Berry, Virginia Gingerick (Box 18)
  - Bertocci, Angelo Philip (Box 18)
  - Bes-Bet (Box 18)
  - Best, Harry (Box 18)
  - Beu - Bh (Box 19)
  - Bevington, Merle Mowbray (Box 19)
  - Bewer, Julius August (Box 19)
  - Bia-Bie (Box 19)
  - Bick, Edgar M. (Box 19)
  - Bidney, David (Box 19)
  - Bieber, Margarete (Box 19)
  - Biel, Ernest (Box 19)
  - Bierstedt, Robert (Box 19)
  - Biesanz, John Berry (Box 19)
  - Big-Bil (Box 20)
  - Bin - Bir (Box 20)
  - Bis - Bj (Box 20)
  - Bishop (Box 20)
  - Bissell, Harold Winthrop (Box 20)
  - Blackm - Blackw (Box 20)
  - Blackmore, Charles P (Box 20)
  - Black (Box 20)
  - Blai - Blan (Box 20)
  - Blair, Paxton (Box 20)
  - Blair, Thomas Marshall Howe (Box 20)
  - Blaisdell, Donald Christy (Box 20)
  - Blaisdell, Thomas Charles (Box 20)
  - Blankenagel, John C. (Box 20)
  - Blanshard, Brand (Box 20)
  - Blanshard, Frances Margaret Bradshaw (Mrs Brand) (Box 20)
  - Blaser, Arthur FrederIck. (Box 20)
  - Blat - Bli (Box 20)
  - Blau, Joseph Leon (Box 20)
  - Bliss, Henry' Evelyn (Box 20)
  - Blitz, Andries (Uitgever, Amsterdam) (Box 20)
  - Blo (Box 21)
  - Bloom, Solomon Frank (Box 21)
  - Blu (Box 21)
  - Bluemel, C S. (Box 21)
  - Blumenthal (Box 21)
  - Bo-Bod (Box 21)
  - Boardman, Fon Wyman (Box 21)
  - Boas, Franz (Box 21)
  - Boas, Frederick Samuel (Box 21)
  - Bode, Carl & Walter Harding (Box 21)
  - Boerker, Richard H. (Box 21)
  - Bog. (Box 21)
  - Boggs, Samuel Whittemore (Box 21)
  - Bogin, Solomon (Box 21)
  - Bogoslovsky, Christina Staël von Holstein (Box 21)
  - Boh - Bok (Box 22)
  - Boisen, Anton T. (Box 22)
  - Bol - Born (Box 22)
  - Bolkestein, Hendrik (Box 22)
  - Bolman, Jr., Frederick deWolfe (Box 22)
  - Bolton (Box 22)
  - Bon (Box 22)
  - Bonbright, James Cummings (Box 22)
  - Bonger, Willem Adriaan (Box 22)
  - Bonthius, Robert Harold (Box 22)
  - Boo (Box 22)
  - Book-of-the--Month Club, Inc. (Box 22)
  - Bor (Box 22)
  - Borek, Ernest (Box 22)
  - Born, Lester K. (Box 22)
  - Barton, Hugh (Box 22)
  - Bos - Bot (Box 22)
  - Botsford, George Willis & E.G. Sihler (Box 22)
  - Bou-Bov (Box 23)
  - Bow-Box (Box 23)
  - Bowden (Box 23)
  - Bowen (Box 23)
  - Bower(s) (Box 23)
  - Bowers, Fredson Thayer (Box 23)
  - Bowlby, John (Box 23)
  - Bowman, Robert (Box 23)
  - Boy - Boz (Box 23)
  - Boyd (Box 23)
  - Boyd, Alice Katharine (Box 23)
  - Bayer, Carl Benjamin (Box 23)
  - Boylan, Marguerite T. (Box 23)
  - Br-Brag (Box 23)
  - Bradbrook, M.C. (Box 23)
  - Bradley (Box 23)
  - Bradshaw, Marion John (Box 23)
  - Brady, Robert Alexander (Box 23)
  - Brai - Bran (Box 24)
  - Braille (Box 24)
  - Bras - Braz (Box 24)
  - Braun, Wilhelm Alfred (Box 24)
  - Bre - Breg (Box 24)
  - Brebner, John Bartlet (Box 24)
  - Breed (Box 24)
  - Brehaut Ernest (Box 24)
  - Bremer, C, Daniel (Box 24)
  - Bren - Bray (Box 24)
  - Brennan, Joseph Gerard (Box 24)
  - Brennecke, Ernest (Box 24)
  - Brenner, Anita (Box 24)
  - Brewer (Box 24)
  - Brewer, Luther Albertus (Box 24)
  - Brewster (Box 24)
  - Brewster, Doroth & John Angus Burrell (Box 24)
  - Bri-Brig (Box 25)
  - Brichta, Rudolph (Box 25)
  - Bridgwater, William & Ralph Foster Weld (Box 25)
  - Briggs (Box 25)
  - Briggs, Lawrence P. (Box 25)
  - Brin - Brit (Box 25)
  - Brissenden, Paul Frederick (Box 25)
  - Bro - Bran (Box 25)
  - Brady, Clara Carnelson (Box 25)
  - Broo - Brou (Box 25)
  - Brook(e)s (Box 25)
  - Brooks, William Keith (Box 25)
  - Broom, Robert (Box 25)
  - Brow; Brown (Box 25)
  - Brown, Alan Willard (Box 25)
  - Brown, Benjamin Houston (Box 25)
  - Brown, Bernard Edward (Box 25)
  - Brown, Deming Bronson & Glenora Washington Brown (Box 25)
  - Brown, Courtney C. (Box 25)
  - Brown, E. Francis (Box 25)
  - Brown, Eleanor Gertrude (Box 25)
  - Brown, Irving Henry (Box 25)
  - Brown, Ralph H. (Box 25)
  - Browne, Rebecca (Box 25)
  - Bru - Brthn (Box 26)
  - Brucker, Herbert (Box 26)
  - Bruen, Alexander J., Jr. (Box 26)
  - Brum-Brut (Box 26)
  - Brunner, Edmund de Schweinitz (Box 26)
  - Bruno, Frank John (Box 26)
  - Bryan(t) (Box 26)
  - Bryan, Alice Isabel, Dorothy Curtiss, & Robert D. Leigh (Box 26)
  - Bryan, William Alfred (Box 26)
  - Brydegaard, Marguerite (Box 26)
  - Bryson, Lyman (Box 26)
  - Bu - Buc (Box 27)
  - Buchier, Justus (Box 27)
  - Buchanan (Box 27)
  - Buck, Arthur Eugene (Box 27)
  - Bud - Buh (Box 27)
  - Buell, Bradley (Box 27)
  - Buerki, Robin C. (Box 27)
  - Bui - Bun (Box 27)
  - Bulletin of Social Legislation of Columbia University (Box 27)
  - Bunim, Miriam Schild (Box 27)
  - Bunzel, Ruth L. (Box 27)
  - Bur-Burg (Box 28)
  - Burch, George Bosworth (Box 28)
  - Burgess (Box 28)
  - Burgess, John William (Box 28)
  - Burke, Arvid James (Box 28)
  - Burke, Edmund (Box 28)
  - Burke, John J. (Box 28)
  - Burke, William Miller (Box 28)
  - Burl - Bum (Box 28)
  - Burinan, Michael & Samuel E. Sinberg (Box 28)
  - Burmeister, Eva Elizabeth (Box 28)
  - Burn (Box 29)
  - Burnett, Philip Mason (Box 29)
  - Burr - Burton (Box 29)
  - Burrow, Trigant (Box 29)
  - Bus - Butc (Box 29)
  - Butler (Box 29)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 29)
  - Butt - Bux (Box 30)
  - Buttinger, Joseph (Box 30)
  - Butzner, Jane (Box 30)
  - By (Box 30)
  - Bychowski, Gustav (Box 30)
  - Bye, Carl Rollinson (Box 30)
  - Byington, Margaret Frances (Box 30)
  - Byrnes, Garrett Davis (Box 30)
  - Ca - Cah (Box 30)
  - Cabeen, David C. (Box 30)
  - Cabot, Hugh (Box 30)
  - Cahill (Box 30)
  - Cal (Box 30)
  - Caidwell (Box 30)
  - Calkins, Gary N. & Francis N. Summers (Box 30)
  - Cam (Box 31)
  - Cameron, Alister (Box 31)
  - Cameron, Gladys (Box 31)
  - Camp, Charles Wellner (Box 31)
  - Campbell, Chambers (Box 31)
  - Campbell, Anna Montgomery (Box 31)
  - Campbell, William V., Robert J, English, & George Lampros (Box 31)
  - Campbell, Robert Francis (Box 31)
  - Can - Cap (Box 31)
  - Cancer Series (Box 31)
  - Chandler Lectures (Box 31)
  - Cannon, Mary Antoinette & Philip Klein (Box 31)
  - Canoutas, Seraphim G. (Box 31)
  - Capozzi, Francis c. (Box 31)
  - Car - Cari (Box 31)
  - Cardozo, Benjamin Nathan (Box 31)
  - Carey (Box 31)
  - Cargill, Oscar (Box 31)
  - Carl (Box 31)
  - Carlson (Box 31)
  - Cariston, Kenneth Smith (Box 31)
  - Carm-Carp (Box 32)
  - Carman, Harry James (With; Paul N. Guthrie; Reinhard H. Luthin; David. King Rothstein; Roy E. Stryker, and Rexford G. Tugwell) (Box 32)
  - Carmichael (Box 32)
  - Carnegie (Box 32)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 32)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (Box 32)
  - Carpenter (Box 32)
  - Caroline Zachry Institute of Human Development (Box 32)
  - Carr (Box 32)
  - Carr (Box 32)
  - Carroll (Box 32)
  - Carroll, Frank S. (Box 32)
  - Carroll, Marie J. (Box 32)
  - Carson (Box 33)
  - Carson, Julia M. H. (Box 33)
  - Carter (Box 33)
  - Carter, Dagny (Mrs Thomas F.) (Box 33)
  - Carter, Thomas Francis (Box 33)
  - Cas-Cask (Box 33)
  - Case, Leslie V. (Box 33)
  - Cass-Cast (Box 33)
  - Cass, Marion T. (Box 33)
  - Cassel, Carl Gustav (Box 33)
  - Castberg, Frede (Box 33)
  - Cat-Cay (Box 33)
  - Cater, Harold D. (Box 33)
  - Cazamian, M & Mine Louis (Box 33)
  - Ce (Box 33)
  - Cha-Cham (Box 34)
  - Chalfant (Box 34)
  - Chamberlain (Box 34)
  - Chamberlain, Lawrence Henry (Box 34)
  - Chamberlain, William Charles (Box 34)
  - Chambers (Box 34)
  - Chamber, Merritt Madison (Box 34)
  - Chambers, Frank Pentland (Box 34)
  - Chan-Chap (Box 34)
  - Chan, Wing-tsit (Box 34)
  - Chandler (Box 34)
  - Chandler Lectures (Box 34)
  - Chang (Box 34)
  - Chao, Ping-lang (Box 34)
  - Chapin (Box 34)
  - Chapman (Box 34)
  - Chapman, John Martin (Box 34)
  - Char-Chat (Box 34)
  - Chase (Box 34)
  - Che (Box 34)
  - Chemistry Lectures (Box 34)
  - Chenault, Lawrence R. (Box 34)
  - Chevalier, Stuart (Box 34)
  - Chia (Box 34)
  - Chiantore, Casa Editrice (Box 34)
  - Chicago (Box 34)
  - Chicago-Cook County Health Survey (Box 34)
  - Chid - Cho (Box 35)
  - Chittick, Victor Lovitt Oakes (Box 35)
  - Chou, Shun-hsin (Box 35)
  - Chr - Chy (Box 35)
  - Christ-Janer, Albert (Box 35)
  - Christie (Box 35)
  - Christy, Arthur E. (Box 35)
  - Chugerman, Samuel (Box 35)
  - Church, Frederic Corss (Box 35)
  - Ci (Box 35)
  - Cla - Clan (Box 35)
  - Clar (Box 35)